[{"answer": "Well, first of all, you know, I do camps, clinics with kids in the North Miami area and Dennis has helped me out.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "You know him, you're a neighbor of his, you live near him, right?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "Nothing.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "But what did you know about North Korea and about the regime?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "Well, I know nothing about Kenny going to North Korea.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "I mean, did you also know nothing about North Korea, about the regime?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "I would have stopped him, correct.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "Would you have stopped him?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "Most people will say look, you know, I don't want to be too harsh on you, Kenny because I know that you're the main culprit here.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "I mean, I think, it's important, you know, that that you recognize that Kenny recognized that there was something wrong with Dennis at that point, right?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "After the game.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "But I felt, you know, that for all these sporting stars to go out there and embrace this guy who is a pretty evil man running a very evil regime that you, yourself, met him Kim Jong-un, and you shook his hand, right?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 94, "question": "Did you know a thing?", "qSentId": 93}, {"answer": "I knew.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "Why am I doing this?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "I had no choice.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "You still shook his hand?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "Because I was -- I feared, you know.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "Why did you have no choice?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "I felt bad.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "Did you feel ashamed as you were doing it?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "First of all, you know, I'm 43 years old, you know.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "Did you feel that Dennis, in a way, sucked you in the something that you just really should never been there?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "They bought it, you know, after ...", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "It must have made your skin crawl there, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "All the information ...", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "When you're watching it now then what do you think?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "Look, can I ask you a question?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "Well, let me ask (inaudible) you came in.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "What does one do?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "It wasn't about the money.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "How much did you guys get paid for this?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "Different guys got different fees.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "But, how much was the fee for the plays that went out there?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "I had a few thousand dollars for it.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "So, if you were being honest, what did you get?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "I got a few thousand dollars for it, $110,000.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "Five, 10?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "I will give a portion to a charity.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 205, "question": "Why don't you give it all to a kid's charity?", "qSentId": 204}, {"answer": "I will give a portion to a charity.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "And not all of it?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "It wasn't about the money in the first place.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "You don't feel comfortable earning money to go on that trip, do you?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "Because I got compensated for doing something.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "Why accept it?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "I'm not in the position to do that.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "Shouldn't you as his agent be recommending or unrecommending that he just basically don't take the money?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "I'm not in the position -- it's his money.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "Or will give it all to charity?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "Well, I did during the campaign against him and the fact of the matter is.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "Given their statement, do you feel that that is a legitimate stick to go after Chris Christie with?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "Well, this is an abuse of power and an attempt to cover up that abuse of power.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "Well I mean that there's a suggestion today that no actual criminal law may have been broken, do you agree with that or do you think that ultimately there may will be a legal case to launch (ph) in a criminal court?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "Well Piers, this is not about polls.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "What do you think is going to happen with this investigation and indeed the political career of Chris Christie?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "John Wisniewski, Assemblyman from New Jersey, thank you very much and Senator Barbara Buono, thank you very much as well.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "He can't run a bridge, how does he want to run a country?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "Because no one wants to go on the record defending something that may ultimately be just proven in a week, or two, or four or six, and that's essentially the problem.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "Why wouldn't they do that?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "Well look, what's taken ahead here is the -- Chris Christie that he wanted to presents nationally.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "So, not much, what does he save for his chances of surviving the scandal, and in fact, continuing to become possibly Republican nominee in 2016?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "Yeah, well, I knew you couldn't quit me, Piers.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "Do you feel there's a double standard here in the way that Democrats are going off to Christie, given the way those three other scandals played out?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "You should, I mean, you should know what's going on and you should also be responsible for the culture that you create in that place.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "... to the actions of people working for you?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "You know, I don't know.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "... to see this as a bit of a side show or not?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "Well, I know that there's a lot of different stories going back and forth, how he has pulled against Hillary Clinton.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "And secondly, perhaps winning a generalization if it was against Hillary Clinton?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "Absolutely, I think that nothing else is going to come up.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "Do you think that he could still be Republican nominee?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "Absolutely, I agree with that.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "So, Ryan, what about you?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "Well, thanks for having me Piers and you know anyone whose covered Roger Ailes knows that he is the most combative man in the American media.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "Are you surprised by the reaction or was that exactly what you expected?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "That's a great fascinating question.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "Why put him on a pedestal of power?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "Well, I think that's a great point.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "Is that true and if he is so powerful, politically, how come he's effectively they lost the last two elections?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "I think that's a fair assessment and that's what my reporting told me after three years in more than 600 interviews.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "Is that fair assessment?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "Well Piers, I reached out to Roger Ailes more than a dozen times in person and in writing.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "How do you plead to that?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "... it's a harrowing story.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "... what did you make about it?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "Listen.", "docId": "140113pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "Final question, is it possible to abhor what Roger Ailes stands for whilst massively admiring his success and ruthless ability to crash rivals?", "qSentId": 579}]